

PROFILE

I am goal driven, passionate ladyseeking for a responsible job with an opportunity for professional challenges and growth. In addition to that, I would like to leverage acquired academic knowledge and work experience in order to help achieve organizational goals.

ID: 92062800541

Drivers License: Learner License

CONTACT

PHONE: +264 85 2018 636 /+264 81 4498288

EMAIL:pexxsheil@gmail.com

INTERESTS

Reading Travelling Volunteerism

REFERENCE

Mr. Nicholas Mukasa Director of Financial Markets Bank of Namibia

Tell: +264 61 2835257

Email: Nicholas.mukasa@bon.com.na

Ms. Sofia N. Malumbu Senior Director: Campus Coordination International University of Management

Tel: +264 65 230145 Cell: +264 81 2222 952

Email: s.malumbu@ium.edu.na

Prof. Arpita Dhar-Ghose Head of Department \Professor Jadavpur University

Tel: +91 33 24146328 Cell: +91 98 30950176

Email: hod@economics.jdvu.ac.in / hod_economics@jdvu.ac.in /

arpitaju@gmail.com

Mr. Sackeus Natangwe Nghimwenavali Corner Coordinator Martin Luther King Jr. Corner: American Space

Tell: +264 65 232017 Cell: +264 81 812 5221

Email: mlkjrcorner2013@gmail.com

VISTORINA MONICA MAGANO NAMBUNDUNGA

EDUCATION

Jadavpur University, India [2015 - 2017] Master of Arts in Economics Polytechnic of Namibia [2011-2014] Bachelor of Technology in Economics Gabriel Taapopi Secondary School [2010] Matric-Commerce

WORK EXPERIENCE

MARTIN LUTHER KING JR.: AMERICAN CORNER [Volunteer]

2019- Present

Helping Peace Corps run the reading club (helping club members with reading, playing games and any other duties delegated to me).

INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF MANAGEMENT [Economics Lecturer]

2018-present

Teaching undergraduate programs, Administering assignments/ tests, setting/marking examinations and research supervision.

BANK OF NAMIBIA [Portfolio Analyst]

04/2015-07/2015

Updating daily security holdings of the bank, improving the existing counterparty folders, updating the audit trial, updating the price and index database and assist with the preparation of the quarterly investment reports and assist with drafting letters and performance memos.

MINISTRY OF FISHERIES AND MARINE RESOURCES [Intern]

02/2014-05/2014

Updating right holder profiles, auditing data inputs for the Fisheries Industry Performance System (FIPS) and drafting letters and memos.

SKILLS

